- 嘿   - 你看 太不可思议了
- Hey.     - Hey, check it out. This is unbelievable.
乔伊已经闭气将近四分钟
Joey has been holding his breath for almost four minutes.
猪头 你想闷死我啊？
Are you trying to kill me?
- 菲比 我问你件事   - 什么事？
- Pheebs, I wanna ask you something.     - Uh-huh, what?
既然我要搬出去 你又这么美丽...
Um, well, since I'm moving out and you're so beautiful...
我搬去跟你住如何？
how about I move in with you?
太好了 但是狄妮丝怎么办？
Well, that would be great, but then what do we do about Denise?
- 谁是狄妮丝？ - 我的室友
- Who's Denise?     - My roommate.
- 你有室友？ - 对 狄妮丝
- You have a roommate?     - Yes, Denise. Denise.
你干嘛这么神秘？
Hey, what is with the secrecy, Phoebe? Huh?
这个狄妮丝可爱吗？
And what about this Denise? She cute?
我们怎么会不知道你有室友？
How can you have a roommate that none of us know about?
也许是因为都没人在听我讲话
Maybe because you never listen to anything I say.
我一天到晚提起她 狄妮丝
I talk about her all the time. Denise!
瑞秋 我在想 我那里会多一个房间
Rach, I was thinking, I'm gonna have an extra room over at my place.
- 没错   - 你何不搬来跟我住？
- Oh, that's true.     - Why don't you move in with me?
多好啊 我们可以熬夜谈心 看电影
It'll be great. We can stay up late talking, watch movies.
你知道赤裸星期四的规定吧？
And you know about naked Thursdays, right?
我还是自己找房子好了
Yeah, yeah, I think I'm gonna find my own place.
我以为赤裸星期四 是我们的专利
Hey, hey. I thought naked Thursdays was just our thing, man.
老友记 第六季 第三集
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
你没办注销 瑞秋怎么说？
What did Rachel say when you told her you were still married to her?
那个啊 她还蛮平静的
Oh, that. Um, she took it really well.
- 你没说 对吧？ - 没有
- Oh. You didn't tell her, did you?     - No.
- 当然没有 因为你爱她   - 我并不爱她
- Because you're in love with her.     - I am not in love with her.
她在为搬家的事难过
She was very upset about having to move out.
所以我没说 免得她更不开心
So I didn't tell her we were still married, because she'd only get more upset.
我只以朋友的身份安慰她
I comforted her. As a friend.
- 什么叫安慰她？ - 也没什么 我抱了抱她
- What do you mean, "comforted her"?     - It was nothing. I gave her a hug.
拥抱正是爱的表示
Aha. A classic sign of love, the hug.
也是友情的表现
It's also a sign of friendship.
在这里不是 痴情男
Yeah, not in your case, Lovey Loverson.
那只是个拥抱
It was a hug.
告诉我 你有没有闻她的头发？
Just tell me this, did you or did you not smell her hair?
闻她的头发？如果有呢？
Smell her hair? Well, what if I did?
九成的女性荷尔蒙散发自头部
Ninety percent of a woman's pheromones come out the top of her head.
所以女人都比较矮
That's why women are shorter.
好让男人在拥抱时爱上她们
So that men will fall in love when they hug them.
拜托 你是科学家耶
Come on, Ross, you're a scientist.
我是以朋友的身份抱她
I was hugging her as a friend, okay?
又不是我把脸埋进她的头发
It's not my fault her hair got in my face.
她的头发很多 有一股...
She's got a lot of it, and it smells all, uh...
椰子香
you know, coconutty.
怎样？那不代表我对她有感觉
What? Oh. It doesn't mean I have feelings for Rachel.
或许我是对椰子有感觉
Maybe it means I have feelings for coconuts.
好 随你怎么说 但你要小心 瑞秋的心情和你不同
Okay, whatever you say. But just be careful. Rachel's not in the same place you are.
如果这个心情是指爱情...
Okay, if the place you're referring to is being in love...
那她和我的心情一样 因为我不是那个心情
then she is in the same place as me, because I am not in that place.
好 我听不懂
Okay, I didn't understand that.
但或许是因为 你讲得是爱的秘语
But maybe that's because you were speaking the secret language of love.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
- 刚才有你的电话   - 是谁？
- Dude, some guy just called for you.     - Who was it?
我哪知？
I don't know.
你怎么不谢我帮你留言？
How about "Thanks for taking the message"? Jeez.
听着
Hey, listen.
等你搬进来 瑞秋的房间就空出来了
When you move in, Rachel's room's gonna be empty.
要不要来讨论怎么利用？
You wanna talk about what we wanna do with it?
- 当然   - 好
- Sure.     - Okay.
我想我们应该弄个漂亮的客房
I think we should have a beautiful guest room...
有红木雪橇床 床头桌上永远插着鲜花
with a mahogany sleigh bed and bedside tables with flowers on them.
再摆张卷盖式书桌放上留官卡
Then we could have a rolltop desk with comment cards...
让客人表达他们的开心
so people can tell us how much they love staying here.
之类的 我还没有想太多
Whatever, you know, I really haven't thought about it that much.
我喜欢这个主意 当然喜欢
Well, I like that idea, obviously. Ha, ha.
我在想或许可以弄个游戏房
But I was thinking maybe it could be a game room, you know?
我们可以买旧的游戏机
I mean, you can buy old arcade games...
像《太空入侵者》和《小行星》
like "Space Invaders" and "Asteroids" for $200.
只要两百元 正港又大台
The real ones. The big, big, big ones.
不要
No.
你的意思是"天哪 钱德 好有趣的主意"
Okay, so you mean "no" as in, "Gee, Chandler, what an interesting idea.
"我们先讨论再全盘否定"
Let's discuss it before we reject it completely."
对不起 当然啦
Oh. I'm sorry. Of course.
很有趣的主意 谈过了 但是不要
Yes. Interesting idea, um, talk about it, but no.
就这样？
So that's it?
漂亮的客房不适合放游戏机
Well, I just don't think that arcade games go in the beautiful guest room.
漂亮的客房里会有很多古董
The guest room's gonna be filled with antiques.
所以《小行星》才适合 那是最古老的游戏机
Which is why "Asteroids" is perfect. It's the oldest game.
你对漂亮的客房有什么意见？
What do you have against the guest room?
我没有意见
I don't have anything against the guest room.
尤其是我们认识的人 都住在方圆数公尺内
Especially since everybody that we know lives about 30 seconds away.
你在嘲笑我吗？
Are you mocking me?
我没有在嘲笑你 或是你漂亮的客房
No, I'm not mocking you or your beautiful guest room.
怎么了？
What's up?
没事 摩妮卡和我吵架了
Nothing. Monica and I had a stupid fight.
但你们还是要同居吧？我的广告今天出来了
But you're still moving in together, right? Because my ad came out today.
"诚征女性室友 不抽烟 不丑"
"Wanted: Female roommate, nonsmoker, nonugly."
- 漂亮   - 啊？
- Nice.     - Ah?
我想说在你之后
I figured after living with you...
换个女室友会蛮有趣的
it'd be an interesting change to have a female roommate.
一个我可以学习 和我不样的人
You know? Someone I could learn from. Someone who's different than me.
谁和我最不一样？年过十九的男人
And what's more different than me, a guy who's not 19...
还是十九岁的女孩？
than, say, a girl who is 19?
哈哈
Ah? Ha, ha.
我可不是草包
Not just a hat rack, my friend.
- 菲比 我想问...   - 嘘 我正在忙
- Pheebs, I have to ask you...     - Shh. I'm swamped right now.
你只是在发呆
You're just staring into space.
我想移动那支铅笔
Um, I'm trying to move that pencil.
- 这支吗？ - 成功了
- This one?     - It worked!
菲比 找房子真是恶梦
Pheebs, this whole apartment thing is a nightmare.
我租得起的地方都有怪胎室友
Every place that I can afford comes with a roommate who is a freak.
你看嘛
Look at this.
"诚征女性室友 不抽烟 不丑"
"Wanted: Female roommate, nonsmoker, nonugly."
- 没房子了 纽约都住满了   - 等等 这里有
- It's just there's nothing. This city is full.     - Wait, no, look at this.
"两房两卫 不得抽烟"
"Two-bedroom, two-bath. Must be nonsmoker.
"拜撒旦者可"
Satan worshipers okay."
不过是一楼
Oh. Yeah, but it's on the ground floor.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
- 瑞秋 你还在找房子？ - 对 怎样？
- Rach, are you still looking for a place?     - Yeah, why?
好 我们博物馆有个华伦
Okay, there's this guy Warren from the museum...
要去参与挖掘工作两年
and he's going on a dig for like two years.
他有个漂亮的家要转租
And he's got this great place he needs to sublet.
你有兴趣吗？
So you interested?
听起来好棒 我愿意住华伦家 我爱华伦
That sounds great. I'd love to live at Warren's. I love Warren.
- 谢谢你   - 别谢我
- Thank you.     - Oh, don't thank me.
如果你想要谢谢谁
You wanna thank someone, thank the volcano...
就谢那座火山几千年前爆靥
that erupted thousands of years ago...
毁灭却也保存了一整个文明
killing but perfectly preserving an entire civilization.
这是华伦的电话
Here's Warren's number.
太好了 我现在就打给他
Oh, this is great. I am gonna call him right now.
- 噢 好   - 谢谢你
- Oh, okay. Oh.     - Thank you. Ha, ha.
好 快去吧
Okay, you go call him.
我看到了
I saw it.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
我在说你知道却不肯承认的事
I'm talking about that which you already know but won't admit.
你又爱上她了 你重复爱她
You know, that you love her again. You relove her.
我没有重复爱她
Look, I do not relove her.
你居然这么嘴硬
I can't believe you won't just admit it.
总之你千万别做蠢事
Okay, just promise me that you won't do anything stupid.
我们现在只是朋友 我为什么要做蠢事？
Look, we're just friends now, okay? Why would I do anything stupid?
房子已经租出去了
Ugh. Well, the apartment is already subletted.
没希望了 我找不到房子了
I mean, this is just hopeless. I'm never gonna find anything.
你可以来跟我住
You can live with me.
- 什么？ - 什么？
- What?     - What?
怎样？
What?
- 天哪 你是说真的吗？ - 嗯哼
- Oh, my God, are you serious?     - Uh-huh.
我求之不得 太好了 谢谢你
I would love to live with you, Ross. That's great. Thank you.
有帮到你就好
I'm just glad I could, you know, help you out.
我真替你们高兴 这真是非常的不蠢
Wow, I'm so happy for you guys. This is so, so not stupid.
罗斯 这对我太重要了
Ross, Ross, you have no idea what this means to me.
我差点就要流落街头 你救了我 你是我的英雄
I mean, I was gonna be homeless. You've just saved me. You're my hero.
说英雄就太... 好吧
Hero? I don't know. Well, all right.
我要去告诉摩妮卡 她的哥哥有多棒
Oh. I have to go tell Monica what a wonderful brother she has.
- 啊   - 别这样
- Aw. Mwah.     - Oh, please.
你又有话要说了吧？
You're gonna say things now, aren't you?
没有...
No. No, I won't.
但是我告诉你
But I should tell you this.
我的室友狄妮丝就是这样
This exact same thing happened to my roommate, Denise.
她搬去跟一个偷娶她的人住
She moved in with a guy...
他嘴上说不爱 其实很爱她
who was secretly married to her and said he didn't love her but really did.
后来事情爆发
It just blew up.
所以她才搬来跟我住
And that's how she ended up living with me.
好吧 我骗你的
Okay, that's a lie.
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hi.     - Hi.
刚才很抱歉 我不需要游戏房
Hi. Listen, I'm sorry about before. I don't need to have a game room.
我以前把不到马子才去打游戏
When I was a kid, I only played those games because I couldn't get girls.
现在我把得到了...
Now I can get...
现在我有了你
Now I have you.
我并不是把你当成
No, not that I think that I have you...
或想成一件财产
or think of you as property in any sort of way.
- 我对女人...   - 别再说了
- I see women...     - Stop it, Chandler.
我也很抱歉
I'm sorry too.
- 真的？ - 对 当然
- Really?     - Yeah. Oh, yes.
哦
Oh.
我们不必弄一个客房
Listen, we don't have to make that a guest room.
- 我们可以一起想要怎么利用   - 好主意
- We can think of something together.     - That's a great idea.
要做到皆大欢喜很容易
We can easily think of a way for us both to enjoy the room.
就是啊
Totally.
- 我们不必现在想   - 好
- We don't have to come up with this now.     - Oh, good.
不如来想想客厅要怎么变化
Why don't we think about changes that we can make in the living room?
变化？
Changes?
对 我们得移动一些家俱 来放我的椅子
Yeah, I mean, we're gonna have to move some furniture to make room for my chair.
你要把懒人椅搬过来？
You're gonna bring the Barcalounger over here?
- 有问题吗？ - 嗯...
- Is that a problem?     - Well...
那是一组的 应该摆在一起
It's just that they're a set and they should probably stay together.
那好 那我就都搬过来
Oh, that's cool. Then I'll just bring them both over.
你是要它们离开老家
See, now you're taking them away from their home.
好 我懂了 这里没我的东西 只有你的东西
Okay, I get it. So I get nothing. Nothing here is mine. Everything is yours.
我早上起床就穿上你的衣服 然后去上班
I'll get up in the morning, put on your clothes, and head off to work.
没错 这里只有我的东西
Yeah. Yeah, you know what? That's it. That's it.
没有你的 这是我说的
Everything will be mine. Nothing will be yours.
拜托 我是在讲懒人椅
Oh, come on. I'm talking about the Barcalounger.
它跟这里不搭 你要摆哪里？
It doesn't match. Where is it gonna go?
游戏房里
In the game room.
你的椅子丑到爆又不是我的错
Look, it is not my fault that your chairs are incredibly ugly.
好 我不搬椅子过来 我什么都不搬过来
That's fine. I won't bring over the chairs. I won't bring anything over.
我可不想破坏老奶奶家的调调
I wouldn't wanna ruin the ambiance over here at Grandma's place!
你的条件看起来很好
Everything on your application looks really good.
最后一个问题
Oh, just one last question.
你和你朋友 会不会常来这里狂欢聚会？
Are you and your friends gonna be over here all the time partying?
放心 我不太爱玩
Oh, don't worry. I'm not really a party girl.
哇
Whoa.
别想都不想就说
Now, don't just be blurting stuff out.
我要你想清楚再答
I want you to really think about your answers.
你不必找室友了 嗨 我要住在这里
You can call off the roommate search. Hi. I'll be living here.
别理他
Oh, don't listen to him.
他很想住进来
He's just some guy who wants the apartment.
但我不会选他
But I don't think he's gonna get it.
你干嘛把浴帘拿掉？
Why did you take the shower curtain down?
那个东西很危险
That thing was a hazard.
我很注重安全
I'm very safety-conscious.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
我正在清些空间给你
Oh, I was just clearing some space for your stuff.
谢谢
Oh, thanks.
但我刚去找摩妮卡
But listen, I was just at Monica's...
她和钱德大吵一架 不同居了
and she and Chandler had a big fight and they're not moving in.
什么叫不同居了？他们还是要同居吧？
What do you mean, not moving in? They're still moving in, right?
不 他们为了怎么利用空房 大吵一架
No, no, they just had a big blowout over what to do with my room.
就为了一个烂房间？
What? Over a stupid room?
我也有点替他们可惜
I feel kind of bad for them...
却又很高兴不必搬过来了
but I'm also psyched because I don't have to move in here.
没错 这一点的确很棒
Oh, no. Yeah. No, that part's great.
你们两个是在吵什么？
What's all this about you guys fighting?
真的就为了一个房间？
Is this really over a room?
真是太傻了
I mean, that is so silly.
- 罗斯 我们自己可以摆平   - 显然不行
- Ross, we can handle this.     - Well, apparently not.
我不能坐视两个我关心的人
And I can't just stand by and watch two people I care about so much...
为了这么傻的事伤感情
be hurt by something that is so silly.
- 别再傻了   - 你叫她别傻啊
- I mean, enough of the silliness.     - Why don't you tell her to stop being silly?
好
Okay, okay.
双方都有理
Two very good points.
我认识你们两个很久了
Look, I've known you both a long time.
你们在一起之后
And I've never seen either of you one-millionth as happy...
比以前快乐一百万倍
as you've been since you got together.
你们真的要为了一个房间 放弃这一切？
Do you really wanna throw that all away over a room?
多傻啊
That is so silly.
什么比较重要
What's more important, love...
爱情还是傻气？
or silliness?
我们喜欢傻气
Well, we are fond of the silliness.
但面对爱情也会心软
But we also have a soft spot for the love.
- 爱是万灵药   - 欢笑才是吧？
- Love is the best medicine.     - That's laughter.
- 你为什么这样？ - 我不知道
- Why do you do it?     - I don't know.
好了 钱德 你想跟摩妮卡住吧？
Now, Chandler, you wanna live with Monica, right?
对
Yeah, I do.
摩妮卡 你想跟钱德住吧？
And, Mon, you wanna live with Chandler, don't you?
对
Yes.
很好 口头契约 在纽约州有约束力
Good. A verbal contract is binding in the state of New York.
中央咖啡厅
我听说你在找房子
So I understand you're looking for a place?
- 不 我不搬了   - 哦
- No, no, I'm staying put.     - Oh.
我本来打算找你来我家住
I was going to offer you my apartment.
为什么？你要去哪里？
Why? Where are you going?
我不知道
I don't know.
- 嘿 瑞秋   - 嗨
- Hey, Rach.     - Hi.
说了你一定不信 钱德和摩妮卡又要同居了
Uh, you're never gonna believe it. Monica and Chandler are moving in again.
真是太好了... 对他们来说 对吧？
That's great news, right? I mean, for them, right?
哦 哇
Oh, wow.
不过好处是 我们又能当室友了
But on the bright side, we get to be roommates again.
是啊 关于这件事...
Yeah. You know, about that, um...
我很感谢你主动提议 但是...
Ross, ahem, I really appreciate your offer to let me move in and everything...
你不觉得会很怪吗？
but don't you think it's gonna be weird?
为什么？为... 为什么会怪？
Why? Why? Why would it...? Why would it be weird?
因为我们...
Well, you know, because of us.
我们的过去
Because of our history.
- 不会   - 不会吗？
- No.     - No?
不会
No, no.
除非我们还余情未了
It would only be weird if we were still in that place.
你还余情未了吗？
I mean, are you still in that place?
- 一点也没有   - 很好 我也没有
- No, not at all.     - Good. Me neither.
那就没问题了
So it's not a problem.
我们只是刚好是室友的朋友
We're just two friends who happen to be roommates.
好 但我们迟早会约会
Okay, but, Ross, eventually, you and I are gonna be dating.
是吗？
Really? We are?
是啊 我会有男朋友 你会有女朋友
Well, yeah. I'm gonna have a boyfriend and you're gonna have a girlfriend.
哦 嘿
Oh. Heh.
那太好了
That'd be great.
不过如果你觉得无所谓 我们就想一套做法
But if you think it's gonna be okay, we'll just work out a system.
就像大学时代 我在门上挂个牌子
It'll be like in college. I'll hang a hanger on the door and put a sign:
"暂且回避 正在炒饭"
"Come back later. I'm getting lucky."
我想都没想过
Yeah, I didn't think of that.
你们确定要住在一起？
So are you sure about this whole moving-in thing?
这是很大的进展 急什么呢？
I mean, it's a really big step. And what's the rush?
真好笑
That's very funny.
他在装傻 因为他知道我们喜欢傻气
He's being silly because he knows we enjoy the silliness.
我是说真的 你们想想
No, I'm serious, okay? I mean, think about it.
你搬进来 你们为了游戏房的事吵架
You move in, you start fighting over stupid game rooms...
接下来就会分手
next thing you know, you break up.
罗斯 你说得对 吵那种架很蠢
Ross, you were right before. It was just a stupid fight about a room.
一点也不蠢
Okay, there are no stupid fights.
重点不是房间
This isn't about the room.
而是房间代表什么
This is about what the room represents.
很不幸的 这个房间会毁了你们
And unfortunately, this room could destroy you.
- 我没那么担心   - 我也是
- Yeah, I'm not so worried.     - Yeah, no, me neither.
好吧 这是你们的人生
Fine. It's your life.
我只是不想看到你们分手
I just don't wanna see you break up.
你们要是同居就会分手
Which you will do if you move in together.
但你们想这样 我也没办法
But if that's what you want, there's nothing I can do.
不要同居
Don't do it!
- 你还是想搬进来吧？ - 当然
- You still wanna move in together, right?     - Of course.
罗斯没吓到你？
Ross didn't scare you?
吓得我死也不敢跟他住
Scared me out of ever wanting to live with him.
- 我给你看个东西   - 好
- Come here, I gotta show you something.     - Okay.
天哪 正方形人被杀了
Oh, my God, someone's killed Square Man.
我觉得懒人椅可以放这里
This is where the Barcalounger could go.
你可以看电视 离厨房又够近
You see, you can see the TV, and still, it's walking distance to the kitchen.
真周到
Oh, that's so sweet.
我也有事要说 好
I wanna show you something.
你知道道路会合的标志吧？
You know those big road signs that say "merge"?
嗯
Mm-hm.
我想我们可以弄一个
You know? So I was thinking we could get one of those signs...
然后挂在床头
and hang it over our bed.
因为你和我就是那样 合而为一
Because that's you and I together.
"道路会合"
"Merge."
- 天哪 我好喜欢喔   - 真的？
- Oh, my God, I love that.     - Really?
才怪
"No."
我发现你在我床上
I found you in my bed
你怎么会在那里？
How'd you wind up there?
你真是个谜
You are a mystery
小黑卷毛男
Little black curly hair
小黑葱毛...
Little black, little black Little black, little black
小黑卷毛男
Little black curly hair
谢谢
Thank you.
嗯...
Um...
如果想收到我的演出电邮讯息
If you wanna receive e-mails about my upcoming shows...
请捐钱给我 让我买电脑
then please give me money so I can buy a computer.
嗯...
So, uh... Ahem.
其他人呢？
Where are the other guys?
摩妮卡和钱德在忙
Well, let's see, Monica and Chandler are occupied.
- 吵架？ - 不 是忙别的
- Fighting?     - No, the other thing.
真高兴他们能和好
I really think it's great they worked things out.
谁也别想拆散他们 对吧？
Yeah, there's no breaking them up, is there?
可以跟你借钥匙去打一副吗？
Hey, can I borrow the key to your house so I can make a copy?
- 当然可以 拿去   - 谢谢
- Here.     - Thank you.
你确定吗？
Now, are you sure?
打了钥匙就不能反悔了
Because once I make a copy, there's no turning back.
我确定
Yeah, I'm sure.
趁我改变心意前快去吧
Now get out of here before I change my mind.
罗斯
Uh, listen, Ross.
跟瑞秋住真的好吗？
You really think this moving in with Rachel is a good idea?
我也在摇摆不定
I've been back and forth.
也许你应该摆回去
Yeah, well, maybe you should go back, okay?
瑞秋搬进去
Rachel moves in, and before you know it...
不知不觉间你们就又复合了
you're where you don't wanna be, back together.
应该不会
Yeah, I don't think so.
她已经在谈交男朋友的事
She's already talking about, you know, dating other guys.
不会有结果的
That's not gonna work out.
她会哭着回家 你会告诉她
Then she's gonna come home all weepy, and you'll be telling her:
"没关系 你会找到好男人"
"Oh, that's okay. You'll find someone."
接着砰 她找到了你
And then, bam, she finds you.
也许你说得对
Huh. Oh, maybe you're right.
我告诉你 罗斯 她绝对会再爱上你
I am telling you, Ross, she is definitely gonna fall in love with you again.
这样你也愿意吗？
Now, is that what you want?
- 我愿意吗？ - 是的
- Heh. Is that what I want?     - Yes.
她来了 我来替你省点事
Here she comes. I'm gonna make your life much easier.
五金行打烊了 改天再打
All right, well, the place was closed, so I'll copy it later.
或是别打了
Or not.
瑞秋 你就搬来跟我住嘛
Uh, Rach, why don't you just move in with me?
- 哈   - 哦
- Ahh.     - Oh.
- 乔伊   - 等等 没关系
- Whoa, whoa, Joey.     - No, no, no. It's okay.
瑞秋 我知道赤裸星期四 把你吓跑了 但是...
Look, Rach, I know I scared you off with that whole naked-Thursdays thing...
我们也可以不做
but we don't have to do that.
搬到对面确实比较轻松
Well, it would be easier to move just right across the hall.
慢着 除非你想改成赤裸星期三
Wait a minute, unless you're thinking about naked Wednesdays.
你不喜欢星期四 那就挑一天
Thursday's clearly not good for you. Pick a day.
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hi.     - Hi.
请进 谢谢你再跑一趟
Come on in. Thanks for coming back.
有很多人想租
Okay, there have been a lot of people interested in the room.
但我经过筛选 你是最后人选之一
But I have narrowed it down, and you are one of the finalists.
- 太好了   - 在做决定之前
- Great.     - Okay, now, before I make my decision...
我想确定我们合得来
I just wanna make sure that our personalities match, okay?
所以我发明了一个小测验
So I made up a little test.
我说一个词 你就说出第一个联想
Now, I'm gonna say a word, and then you say the first thing that comes to mind.
- 没问题   - 好 那我们开始
- I can do that.     - Okay, here we go.
- 枕头   - 仗
- Pillow.     - Fight.
很好
Very good.
好 丁字
Okay. G.
- 裤？ - 非常好
- String?     - Excellent.
好...
Okay. Um...
狗
Doggy.
- 猫？ - 很抱歉
- Kitten?     - Ooh, sorry.
就差那么一点点 再见
No, no, no. So close, though. But, you know, okay, bye-bye.